export const questions = [
    {
        question: "What is the correct command to create a new React-vite project?",
        option1: "npm create-react-app reactAppName",
        option2: "npm create vite@latest reactAppName",
        option3: "npx create vite@latest appName",
        option4: "npm create vite reactAppName",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "What is JSX?",
        option1: "JSX is a syntax extension of JavaScript.",
        option2: "JSX is a javascript library",
        option3: "JSX is a front-end tool",
        option4: "None of the above",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "What command is used to start the React-vite local development server?",
        option1: "npm serve",
        option2: "npm run dev",
        option3: "npm build",
        option4: "npm start",
        ans: 2,
    },{
        question: "What is the default local host port that a React development server uses?",
        option1: "3000",
        option2: "3500",
        option3: "5000",
        option4: "8080",
        ans: 1,
    },{
        question: "To develop and run React code, Node.js is required.",
        option1: "True",
        option2: "False",
        ans: 2,
    },{
        question: "What is the children prop?",
        option1: "A property that lets you pass data to child components",
        option2: "A property that lets you set an object as a property",
        option3: "A property that lets you nest components in other components",
        option4: "A proprty that adds child values to state",
        ans: 1,
    },{
        question: "Which keyword creates a constant in JavaScript?",
        option1: "let",
        option2: "var",
        option3: "constant",
        option4: "const",
        ans: 4,
    },{
        question: "A copy of the 'real' DOM that is kept in memory is called what?",
        option1: "Shadow DOM",
        option2: "Virtual DOM",
        option3: "React DOM",
        option4: "DOM",
        ans: 2,
    },{
        question: "Which operator can be used to conditionally render a React component?",
        option1: "&&",
        option2: "::",
        option3: "||",
        option4: "??",
        ans: 1,
    },{
        question: "When rendering a list using the JavaScript map() method, what is required for each element rendered?",
        option1: "id",
        option2: "data",
        option3: "index",
        option4: "key",
        ans: 4,
    }
    
]